The kid's coming with me.
这孩子跟我走
Who's he tracking?
他在追踪谁
The kid.
孩子
Then they’ll keep coming.
他们不会罢休的
Yes.
嗯
Mando.
曼达人
Is that you under that bucket?
那桶似的头盔下面是你吗
Ran.
兰恩
I didn't really know
我都不确定
if I'd ever see you in these parts again.
是否还能在这一带见到你
Good to see you.
见到你真好
You know, to be honest,
说实话
I was a little surprised when you reached out to me.
你和我联系时  我还有点吃惊呢
You know, 'cause I... I hear things.
因为我...  有所耳闻
Like, maybe things between you and the Guild aren't workin' out.
好像你和公会搞僵了
I'll be fine.
我不会有事的
Okay. Well, you know the policy.
好吧  你知道规矩
No questions.
不该问的不问
And you, you're welcome back here anytime.
而你呢  随时欢迎你回这里
So, what's the job?
是什么活
Yeah, one of our associates ran afoul of
我们的一个手下和竞争者
some competitors and got himself caught.
起了争执  人被抓起来了
So, I'm puttin' together a crew to spring him.
我在组建个团队去救他
It's a five person job. I got four.
五个人的活  我这有四个人
All I need is the ride, and you brought it.
我需要的是交通工具  而你开来了
The ship wasn't part of the deal.
飞船不包括在这单生意里
Well, the Crest is the only reason I let you back in here.
我允许你回来都是因为刀锋之巅
What's the look?
什么表情
Is that gratitude?
是感恩吗
Uh-huh. I think it is.
我感觉是
Hey, Mayfeld.
梅菲尔德
Yeah?
干嘛
This is Mando, the guy I was tellin' you about.
这是我和你说过的那个曼达人
We used to do jobs way back when...
我们曾一起干事  那还是...
This is the guy?
就是他啊
Yeah, we were all young, tryin' to make a name for ourselves.
嗯  那时我们都血气方刚  想要扬名立万
Yeah, but runnin' with a Mandalorian, that was...
可和一个曼达洛人闯荡  那...
That brought us some reputation.
那确实让我们有了点名气
Oh, yeah? What did he get out of it?
是吗  那对他有什么好处
I asked him that one time. You remember what you said, Mando?
我曾经问过他  你还记得你怎么回答的吗
Target practice.
打靶练习
We did some crazy stuff, didn't we?
我们做过些疯狂事  是不是
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前的事了
Well...
是啊...
Well, I don't go out anymore. You understand?
我不去外面折腾了  你明白吗
So, uh, Mayfeld, he's gonna run point on this job.
所以这个事由梅菲尔德负责
If he says it, it's like it's comin' from me.
他下的命令就等于是我下的
You good with that?
你没问题吧
You tell me.
我不知道
You haven't changed one bit.
你一点都没变
Yeah, well, things have changed around here.
这里的情况已经不同了
Yeah, well, Mayfeld, he's...
梅菲尔德  他...
He's one of the best triggermen I've ever seen.
他是我见过的最棒的枪手
Former Imperial sharpshooter.
前帝国的神枪手
That's not saying much.
那也没什么光彩的
I wasn't a stormtrooper, wiseass.
我不是暴风兵  自以为是的家伙
Don't take long, does it?
够快的  是吧
Razor Crest? I can't believe that thing can fly.
刀锋之巅  这玩意还能飞啊
Looks like a Canto Bight slot machine.
看着就像坎托拜那里的老虎机一样
The good-lookin' fellow there with the horns, that's Burg.
那个长角的帅哥叫伯格
This may surprise you, but he's our muscle.
你可能想不到  他是我们的打手
So, this is a Mandalorian.
这是个曼达洛人
I thought they'd be bigger.
我以为他们是大块头呢
Droid's name is Zero.
机器人叫零
I thought you said you had four.
你不是说你有四个人吗
He does.
没错
Hello, Mando.
你好  曼达人
Xi'an.
希安
Tell me why I shouldn't cut you down where you stand?
给我个理由不就地把你砍翻在地
Nice to see you, too.
见到你我也很高兴
I missed you.
我挺想你
This is shiny.
这真亮啊
You wear it well.
你穿着不错
Do we need to leave the room or something?
我们是不是应该回避一下
Well, Xi'an's been a little heartbroken
曼达人离开我们的团队以后
since Mando left our group.
希安有点伤心
Aw. You gonna be okay, sweetheart?
你会没事吧  宝贝
Oh, I'm all business now.
我现在很一本正经的
Learned from the best.
从最好的师傅那学来的
All right, lovebirds.
好吧  小情侣
Break it up till you get on the ship.
等我们上了飞船你们再腻味吧
Right now we don't have much time.
现在我们没时间
Tiny.
真小
Fuel.
燃料
Navigation. Hyperdrive.
导航  曲速
Landing gear.
起落架
Comms.
通讯装置
Mando...
曼达人
I received... I received wonderful news.
我得到了好消息
Upon your... Upon your... Deliver the quarry. Deliver the...
在你...你的...  递交猎物...
So, the package is being moved on a fortified transport ship.
目标正在一艘被加固过的运输飞船上
Now, we got a limited window to board, find our friend,
我们只有很短的时间可以登机  找到我们的朋友
get him out of there before they make their jump.
在他们进入曲速之前救出他
That's a New Republic prison ship.
这是新共和国的监狱船
Your man wasn't taken by a rival syndicate. He was arrested.
你的人不是被对立集团带走了  而是被逮捕了
So what?
那又如何
A job is a job.
你已经接下任务了
That's a max security transport
这是最高安全级别的运输舰
and I'm not looking for that kinda heat.
我不想惹这种麻烦
Well, neither are we. So just don't mess up.
我们也不想  所以别搞砸
The good news for you is the ship is manned by droids.
好消息是  这艘飞船是由机器人操控的
Still hate the machines, Mando?
你还是很讨厌机器  对吗  曼达人
Despite recent modifications,
虽然最近进行过修整
the ship is still quite a mess.
这艘飞船的情况还是一团糟
The power lines are leaking, the navigation is intermittent,
输电线在漏电  导航系统断断续续
and the hyperdrive is only operating at 67.3% efficiency.
曲速的运行效率只有67.3%
We have much better ships. Why are we using this one?
我们有更好的飞船  为什么还要用这一艘
'Cause the Razor Crest is off
因为刀锋之巅已经脱离了
the old Imperial and the New Republic grid.
老帝国和新共和国的监控范围
It's a ghost.
就是一艘影子飞船
Yeah, and we need a ship that can get close enough
没错  我们需要一艘可以足够接近监狱船
to jam New Republic code.
并且干扰新共和国暗码的飞船
So, when we drop out of hyperspace here,
当我们在这里脱离曲速
if we immediately bank into this kinda attitude,
我们会立刻达到到这里的海拔
we should be right in their blind spot,
应该可以直接进入他们的盲点
which will give us just enough time
这可以给我们争取足够的时间
for your ship to scramble our signal.
来让你的飞船隐藏我们的信号
It's not possible. Even for the Crest.
这不可能  连刀锋之巅也做不到
That's why he's flyin'.
所以才要他来驾驶
Mando, I know you're a pretty good pilot,
曼达人  我知道你是个很优秀的飞行员
but we need you on the trigger. Not on the wheel.
但我们需要你执行任务  而不是驾驶飞船
Don't worry, Mandalorian.
别担心  曼达洛人
My response time is quicker than organics.
我的反应时间比有机生命体更快
And I'm smarter, too.
而且我更聪明
All right. I-- Yeah. That's good.
好了  可以了
Forgive the programming. He's a little rough around the edges.
请原谅  他的程序还是有些不完善
But he is the best.
但他确实是最出色的
How can you trust it?
你怎么能相信它
You know me, Mando. I don't trust anybody.
你了解我  曼达人  我不相信任何人
Just like the good old days, Mando. Huh?
就像过去的美好时光  曼达人  对吗
Will you sit down?
你能坐下吗
Calculations complete.
计算完成
Jumping to hyperspace now.
现在开始进入曲速
Feel free to join the others. I will handle it from here.
你可以和他们会合了  后面交给我
Hey, hey, hey. Okay. Okay. Okay, I get it.
好了  好了  我明白
I'm a little particular about my personal space, too.
我对私人空间也很敏感
So, let's just do this job.
我们做任务就好
We get in, we get out,
进去  出来
and you don't have to see our faces anymore.
然后你也不必再见到我们了
Someone tell me why we even need a Mandalorian.
告诉我  我们为什么需要曼达洛人
Well, apparently they're the greatest warriors in the galaxy.
很显然  他们是星系最勇猛的战士
So they say.
别人是这么说的
Then why are they all dead?
那他们怎么都死了
Well, you flew with him, Xi'an.
你和他一起飞行过  希安
Is he as good as they say?
他和他们说的一样厉害吗
Ask him about the job on Alzoc III.
问问他阿尔佐克三号星上的任务
I did what I had to.
我做了我必须做的事
Oh, but you liked it.
但你很享受
See, I know who you really are.
我知道你到底是什么人
He never takes off the helmet?
他从没摘下过头盔吗
This is the Way.
此乃正道
I wonder what you look like under there.
我很好奇你到底长什么样
Maybe he's a Gungan.
也许他是冈根人
Is that why yousa don't wanna show your face?
难道这就是你不愿意露脸的原因
You ever seen his face?
你见过他的脸吗
A lady never tells.
女人从不泄密
Aw. Come on, Mando. We all gotta trust each other here.
曼达人  我们得互相信任
You gotta show us somethin'.
你总得让我们见识见识
Come on. Just lift the helmet up.
来吧  把头盔抬起来
Come on.
来吧
Let's all see your eyes.
让我们看看你的眼睛
I'll do it.
我来
Whoa! What is that?
那是什么
You get lonely up here, buddy? Huh?
你在这很寂寞吗  小家伙
Wait a minute. Did you two make that? Huh?
等等  这是你们俩生的吗
What is it, like a pet or somethin'?
这是什么  宠物吗
Yeah. Something like that.
是的  差不多
Didn't take you for the type.
没看出来你是这种人
Maybe that code of yours has made you soft.
也许是你的准则让你心软了
Me, I was never really into pets.
我从来就不喜欢宠物
Yeah, I didn't have the temperament. Patience, you know?
我没那个耐心
I mean, I tried, but never worked out.
我试着养过  也没什么结果
But I'm thinkin'
但我在考虑
maybe I'll try again with this little fella.
也许我可以试着再养一次这个小家伙
Dropping out of hyperspace now.
现在开始脱离曲速
Commencing final approach, now.
现在开始最终着陆
Cloaking signal, now.
现在开始隐蔽信号
Engaging coupling now.
现在准备对接
Coupling confirmed. We are down.
对接确认  我们落地了
And relax.
放松
Commence extraction now.
开始营救任务
Useless droid didn't even give us a proper countdown.
废物机器人甚至都没给我们认真倒计时
Z, are you sure they can't see us?
零  你确定他们看不到我们吗
The Razor Crest is scrambling our signature
刀锋之巅扰乱了我们的信号
and I am inside the prison system.
我入侵进了监狱系统
It's impressive that this gunship had survived the Empire
这艘炮舰居然幸存了下来
without being impounded.
没有被帝国扣押  真是太厉害了
All right, we got a job to do. Mando, you're up.
好了我们有工作要做  曼达人  该你了
- It's me? - Always you.
-是我吗  -一直都是你
Zero.
零
Get us to the control room.
带我们去控制室
Sub level three. Disabling onboard surveillance.
向下三层  正在关闭舰内监控
All right, we're on the clock.
好吧  我们时间紧迫
When we engage those droids, they're gonna be all over us.
当我们和那些机器人交战时  它们会一拥而上
I know the drill.
我知道这个套路
Bio trackers activated.
生物追踪器激活
I've got eyes.
我有眼睛
All right, let's go.
好吧  我们走
- I don't like this. - You always were paranoid.
-我不喜欢这个感觉  -你总是多疑
Is that true, Mando? Were you always paranoid?
是真的吗  曼达人  你总是多疑吗
Approaching control room. Make a left at the next juncture.
接近控制室  在下一个路口向左拐
What? It's just a little mousey.
怎么了  只是个小老鼠
- Come here, little mousey. - Burg.
-过来  小老鼠  -伯格
No! Burg, what are you doin'?
不  伯格  你在干什么
What?
怎么了
Intruder alert. Open fire.
入侵者警报  开火
We're too exposed here.
我们这里太暴露了
If they get a signal out, it's not gonna matter.
如果他们发出信号  那就没关系了
Mando, let's go! You're supposed to be somethin' special.
曼达人  上啊  你应该是个狠角色
I knew it. I knew it!
我就知道  我就知道
Make sure you clean up your mess.
记得把你的烂摊子收拾干净
It seems your presence has been detected.
看来你们的存在被发现了
Redirecting security alert away from your position.
将安全警报从你们的位置重移开
Z, open the door!
零  开门
But I'm detecting an organic signature.
但我发现了一个有机体信号
Yeah, okay. All right. Just open the door!
行了知道了  把门打开
Stop!
站住
Just stop right there.
就停在那儿
You put down the blasters right now.
立刻放下枪
Nice shoes.
鞋子不错
Put down your blasters.
放下你的枪
Matches his belt.
跟他的腰带很配啊
There were only supposed to be droids on this ship.
这艘舰上应该只有机器人的
Hang on, hang on. Let's see here. Uh...
等等  等等  我们看看
Cell two-two-one.
二二一号房
All right, now for our well-dressed friend.
好吧  现在给我们穿着考究的朋友
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey. Easy. Easy, egghead.
慢着慢着  放松  蛋头
Put that down. Put that down. Come on.
把它放下  把它放下  快点
Easy. Put it down now!
放松  快放下
Easy. Nobody has to get hurt here. Just calm down.
放松  不用有人受伤  冷静
What is that thing?
那是什么东西
It's a tracking beacon.
这是一个跟踪信标
He presses that thing, we're all done.
他按那个键  我们都得死
A New Republic attack team will hone in on that signal
新共和国的攻击群会循迹而来
and blow us all to hell.
把我们炸成渣
Put it down!
放下它
Are you serious?
你是认真的吗
Yes, I'm serious.
是的  我是认真的
You didn't think we needed to know that tiny little detail?
你以为我们不需要知道那个小细节
I didn't think we'd get to this point.
我没想到我们会走到这一步
Yet here we are.
但我们确实走到了
Are you questioning my managerial style, Xi'an?
你在质疑我的管理风格吗  希安
No, sir.
没有  长官
Hey. Listen to me.
嘿  听我说
Hey, hey, hey. Listen to me, okay?
嘿  听我说  好吗
Look.
听我说
- Hey. Put it down. - Are you crazy?
-嘿  把枪放下  -你疯了吗
put it down.
放下枪
What's your name?
你叫什么名字
- It's Davan. - Davan.
-我是达文  -达文
We're not here for you. We're here for a prisoner.
我们不是来抓你的  我们是来救犯人的
If you let us go about our job, you can walk away with your life.
如果你让我们完成任务  你可以活着离开
No, he won't.
不  他不会的
You realize what you're gonna bring down on us?
你知道你会给我们带来什么吗
You think I care about that?
你觉得我在乎吗
We're not killing anybody, you understand?
我们不会杀人  懂吗
Get that blaster out of my face, Mando.
把枪从我脸上拿开  曼达人
I can't do that.
我不能那样做
Don't.
不要
Would you both just shut up?
你们都闭嘴好吗
Crazy Twi.
疯狂的老提
I had it under control.
我刚才控制住局面了
Yeah. Looked like it.
真棒  看起来控制住了
Was that thing blinking before?
那东西以前在闪吗
Was it?
有吗
- Zero to Mayfeld. Zero to Mayfeld. - What?
-零呼叫梅菲尔德  -怎么了
I've detected a New Republic distress signal
我发现你们的位置上
homing in on your location.
有一个新共和国求救信号
You have approximately 20 minutes.
你大概有20分钟
We only need five.
我们只需5分钟
Let's go, let's go. Move, move, move!
我们走  快  快  快
Z, open it up.
零  打开
- You have 15 minutes remaining. - Come on, come on.
-你还有15分钟  -快点  快点
Open it up!
打开
Qin.
秦
Funny, the man who left me behind is now my savior.
真有趣  那个丢下我的人现在成了我的救世主
Mando.
曼达人
- Brother! - Sister.
-哥哥  -妹妹
Attack's on the way. He's already dead meat. Let's go!
这里马上就会受到攻击  他死定了  走吧
Come on, it's better this way.
这样最好
You deserve this!
活该
Let's go!
走吧
Mando. Mando?
曼达人  曼达人
I've received your transmission.
我已收到你的信息
Upon your return, deliver the quarry directly to the client.
你回来后  把猎物直接交给客户
Interesting.
有趣
Zero, we got Qin.
零  我们找到秦了
I found some information on The Mandalorian.
我找到了曼达洛人的资料
From the Bounty Hunters Guild.
来自赏金猎人协会
Yeah, do whatever. Just get us off this ship.
随便啦  快让我们离开飞船
You have 10 minutes remaining.
你还有10分钟
- Zero to Mayfeld. Zero to Mayfeld. - Wait, wait, wait!
-零呼叫梅菲尔德  -等等  等等
- Yeah? - You have a potential problem.
-怎么了  -有个隐患
He has escaped.
他逃走了
- I told you we should've ended him. - I know!
-我就说应该干掉他吧  -我知道
- This is your fault! - I know!
-这是你的错  -我知道
- Go! Go, go, go! - Come on!
-走  快  快  -快走
- No! - No!
-不  -不
No! Burg! Burg!
不  伯格  伯格
Zero to Mayfeld. Mayfeld, do you copy?
零呼叫梅菲尔德  梅菲尔德  收到吗
It seems comms are no longer functioning,
通讯好像失效了
therefore you cannot hear me.
所以你听不见我说话
You are on your own.
只能靠你们自己了
Curious.
有趣
It's all right. You and the Devaronian, split up.
没关系  你和德瓦隆人分头行动
Find Mando and kill him.
找到曼达人  杀了他
Then find a way back to the ship!
然后想办法回飞船
Zero! We need a path.
零  帮我们指条路
Zero!
零
Do you have a name?
你有名字吗
Mayfeld.
梅菲尔德
Well, Mr. Mayfeld, you're gonna get me the hell off this ship.
梅菲尔德先生  赶紧帮我离开这艘飞船
Hey, wait. What about your sister?
等等  你妹妹怎么办
What about her?
什么怎么办
Nice family.
家人关系真棒
Mando always did hate droids.
曼达人一直很讨厌机器人
Z?
零
Whatever Ran promised, I'll see to it you get triple share.
不管兰恩承诺了什么  我给你三倍
Just get him.
抓住他
You better be good for it.
希望你付得起
Mando.
曼达人
Where are you, little mouse?
你在哪里  小老鼠
Let's see your face, Mandalorian.
让我看看你的脸  曼达洛人
Zero, where is he?
零  他在哪里
What the...
什么
No!
不
Qin.
秦
You killed the others.
你杀了其他人
They got what they deserved.
他们是罪有应得
You kill me, you don't get your money.
你杀了我就拿不到钱
Whatever Ran promised, I'll make sure you get it, and more.
不管兰恩承诺了什么  我都会给你更多
Come on, Mando.
拜托  曼达人
Be reasonable.
理智点
You were hired to do a job, right?
你是受雇抓猎物的吧
So do it.
那就抓我吧
Isn't that your code?
这不是你的准则吗
Aren't you a man of honor?
你不是个有荣誉感的人吗
Where are the others?
其他人呢
No questions asked. That's the policy, right?
不问问题  这是规矩  对吧
Yeah. That is the policy.
没错  这就是规矩
I did the job.
我完成了任务
Yeah, you did.
是的  你完成了
Just like the good old days.
就像过去的美好时光
Yeah, just like the good old days.
是啊  就像过去的美好时光
Kill him.
杀了他
What's this?
这是什么
That bastard.
那个混蛋
I got a clear signal on the tracking beacon.
跟踪信标有一个清晰信号
Copy that.
收到
Are those X-wings?
那是X翼战机吗
Yep. That's definitely a tracking beacon.
是的  那绝对是跟踪信标
Looks like they're launching a gunship.
看起来他们在发射炮艇机
Copy. Goin' in.
收到  上吧
I told you that was a bad idea.
我说了这是个坏主意